Travis Schram

600 S. Miller Rd Saginaw, MI. 48609

LinkedIn: <u>Travis Schram</u> | Github: <u>TSchram</u> | <u>Portfolio</u>

E-Mail: TSchram93@gmail.com | Phone: (989)284-2576

Objective

I desire a position that will allow me the opportunity to develop the skills necessary to reach my full potential. I am a hard worker with a passion to build upon my personal and professional growth within your organization. My participation in High School athletics, as well as my prior employment experience has helped me to develop a strong team mentality and I look forward to the opportunity to bring this dedication to your team.

Education

09/2008 - 06/2012

Swan Valley High School

Saginaw, MI

High School Diploma

Coursework: Advanced Mathematics

Academic Awards/Achievements: Merit Role

Experience

11/2013 - 08/2020	Selector – Gordon Food Service	Brighton, MI
12/2010 - 11/2013	Sales Associate - Gordon Food Service Marketplace	Saginaw, MI
08/2020-Current	Warketplace	Saginaw, MI
	Independent Contractor	

Computer Skills

- HTML
- Cascading Style Sheets
- Javascript
- API Web Integration

Involvement/Activities

•	Swan Valley Freshman Football	2008-2009
•	Swan Valley J.V. Football	2009-2010
•	Swan Valley Varsity Football	2010-2012
•	Voluntary Community Service	2008-2012

References

References are available on request.